<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tesco training</title><link>http://example.org/</link><description>Recent content on Tesco training</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 14:10:13 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Java</title><link>http://example.org/posts/my-firstpost/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/posts/my-firstpost/</guid><description>Chapter 1 Basics Discover what this Java is all about and the core-concepts behind it.</description></item><item><title>Objects</title><link>http://example.org/java/object/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 14:10:13 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/java/object/</guid><description>Java is an Object-Oriented Language. As a language that has the Object-Oriented feature, Java supports the following fundamental concepts −
Polymorphism Inheritance Encapsulation Abstraction Classes Objects Instance Method Message Passing In this chapter, we will look into the concepts - Classes and Objects.
Object − Objects have states and behaviors. Example: A dog has states - color, name, breed as well as behaviors – wagging the tail, barking, eating.</description></item><item><title>Basicsyntax</title><link>http://example.org/java/basicsyntax/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 14:09:53 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/java/basicsyntax/</guid><description>When we consider a Java program, it can be defined as a collection of objects that communicate via invoking each other&amp;rsquo;s methods. Let us now briefly look into what do class, object, methods, and instance variables mean.
objects − Objects have states and behaviors. Example: A dog has states - color, name, breed as well as behavior such as wagging their tail, barking, eating. An object is an instance of a class.</description></item><item><title>Overview</title><link>http://example.org/java/overview/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 14:09:27 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/java/overview/</guid><description>Java programming language was originally developed by Sun Microsystems which was initiated by James Gosling and released in 1995 as core component of Sun Microsystems' Java platform (Java 1.0 [J2SE]).
The latest release of the Java Standard Edition is Java SE 8. With the advancement of Java and its widespread popularity, multiple configurations were built to suit various types of platforms. For example: J2EE for Enterprise Applications, J2ME for Mobile Applications.</description></item><item><title>Javascript</title><link>http://example.org/posts/javascript/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2021 15:37:05 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/posts/javascript/</guid><description>Java is a good programming language</description></item></channel></rss>